<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<blockquote class="stu-note">
		<p>In this version of the guide the Medication Summary is expressed as a list of MedicationStatements. The reason for this choice is explained in the <a href="design.html#the-use-of-medication-statements-in-the-summary">Design Conventions and Principles</a> page.</p>
		<p>STU implementers are encouraged to provide their feedback about this design choice.</p>
	</blockquote>
	<blockquote class="stu-note">
		<p>In this version of the guide the Immunizations section has been extended to also include, when relevant, the status of immunity to specific target diseases.
		The section description has been revised to <i>IPS Immunizations/Immune Status Section</i> to reflect this (a status of immunity to a disease is the intended and desired outcome of a vaccinaation).
		The capability to record a statement of immunity to a disease and the supporting data for that statement is provided by a profile on the Condition resource, using specific "immune status" codes.</p>
		<p>The Condition resource was chosen to represent the immune status, as immunity (including, in some cases, "no immunity") is an ongoing state of the patient.  It is not simply an observation at a point in time,
		although those observations will often be associated with the condition and are used to provide supporting evidence for it.
		This capability is especially relevant and needed at the present time for recording immunity to the COVID-19 disease caused by the SARS-CoV-2 virus.</p>
		<p>The preferred codes have been chosen from the 'Finding of immune status' hierarchy in SNOMED CT.  Most of these codes are not currently included in the SNOMED CT Global Patient Set (GPS), and it is possible instead
		to use additional supplemental codes or to choose alternative codes.  A code for representing a condition of immunity to COVID-19 has not yet been developed and made available in SNOMED CT,
		so at this time FHIR codes for representing both immunity and also non-immunity to COVID-19 have been included in the value set.</p>
		<p>Comments are welcome and implementers of this STU are encouraged to provide their feedback about these design choices.</p>
		<p>This proposed solution will be also subject to evaluation by the wider cross-SDO IPS community, in order to assure a complete alignment among the different IPS standards; it is therefore potentially subject to change.</p>
	</blockquote>
</div>
