<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<blockquote class="stu-note">
		<p>In this version of the guide the Medication Summary is expressed as a list of MedicationStatements. The reason for this choice is explained in the <a href="design.html#the-use-of-medication-statements-in-the-summary">Design Conventions and Principles</a> page.</p>
		<p>STU implementers are encouraged to provide their feedback about this design choice.</p>
	</blockquote>
	<blockquote class="stu-note">
		<p>Particularly in light of the currect state of global health and the response to the COVID-19 pandemic 
		due to the SARS-CoV-2 virus, extending the IPS Immunizations section to also include, when relevant, the status of 
		immunity to specific target diseases is being considered.  The potential updates to this implementation guide to 
		incorporate this capability are still being discussed and have not been included in this initial published version of 
		the guide.  These proposed updates may include revising the Immunization section description to reflect this 
		broadened scope (as <i>IPS Immunizations/Immune Status Section</i>, or similar), as a presumed or verified status of 
		immunity to a disease is, in fact, the intended and desired outcome of a vaccination/immunization.</p>
		<p>The capability to record a statement of immunity to a disease could be provided via a profile on the Condition
		resource and specific "immune status" codes (a set of "Finding of immune status" codes is currently available in 
		SNOMED CT - however, at this time, a code representing "Immunity to COVID-19" or the equivalent is not available).  
		The Condition resource may be appropriate for this purpose, as immunity (including, in some cases, a statement of 
		"no immunity") is an ongoing state of the patient for some period of time (once immunity is acquired, typically for
		multiple years).  The statement of immunity is not simply an observation at a point in time, although a statement of 
		immunity would be expected in the case of COVID-19 and in many or most other cases to have associated observations 
		that are necessary for providing the supporting evidence for the "immunity" condition.</p>
		<p>As specific profiling is not yet available in the current IG publication to support the representation of a 
		statement of immunity, the open slicing approach for including additional data in an IPS instance may be used.  An 
		example of of how this might be done is available in the 'immune-status' and potentially other branches of the IPS 
		IG specification continuous integration (CI) build - link available by request from 
		<a href="mailto:ips@lists.hl7.org">ips@lists.hl7.org</a> or in the FHIR Zulip chat <i>IPS Community of Practice</i> 
		<a href="https://chat.fhir.org/#narrow/stream/207835-IPS">stream</a>.</p>
		<p>Reviewers and implementers of this STU are encouraged to provide their feedback about this need and any questions, 
		suggestions or concerns regarding the example profiles or other alternative approaches to addressing this situation.  
		Any proposed solutions to be considered for inclusion in a future version of this guide will be subject to evaluation 
		by the wider cross-SDO IPS community as well as the broader standards community and where possible relevant public 
		health authorities (global, national and regional), in order to ensure to the extent possible that any solution that 
		is adopted will be appropriate, usable and clinically sound.</p>
	</blockquote>
</div>
